A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, International Relations, RG 1.3, Series 155 FA388A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Relations, 1971-1989; 155
  - (489) – University of Natal: Built Environment Support Group, 1986 February-August (Box 116, Folder 1167)
  - (489) – University of Natal: Built Environment Support Group, 1986 October-1988 December (Box 116, Folder 1168)
  - University of Notre Dame: Anti-Nuclear Conference, 1982-1985 (Box 116, Folder 1169)
  - University of Notre Dame: Multinational Corporations: Front of File, 1984, 1988, 1990 (Box 116, Folder 1170)
  - University of Notre Dame: Multinational Corporations, 1982 August-1983 June (Box 116, Folder 1171)
  - University of Notre Dame: Multinational Corporations, 1983 September-1984 October (Box 116, Folder 1172)
  - University of Notre Dame: Multinational Corporations, 1985 April-1986 December (Box 116, Folder 1173)
  - University of Notre Dame: Multinational Corporations, 1987 March-1988 September (Box 116, Folder 1174)
  - University of Notre Dame: Multinational Corporations: Supplementary Material (I): "Multinational Managers and Poverty in the Third World", edited by Lee A. Tavis, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 1175)
  - University of Notre Dame: Multinational Corporations: Supplementary Material (II): Center for the Study of Man in Contemporary Society Newsletter, Vol. l, No. 1, Fall 1981 (Box 117, Folder 1176)
  - University of Notre Dame: Multinational Corporations: Supplementary Material (III): "Multinational Managers and Host Government Interactions", edited by Lee A. Tavis, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 1177)
  - University of Notre Dame: Multinational Corporations: Supplementary Material (IV): "Rekindling Development: Multinational Firms and World Debt", edited by Lee A. Tavis, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 1178)
  - University of Pittsburgh: Caribbean Basin Conference: Front of File and Evaluation, 1982, 1985-1986 (Box 117, Folder 1179)
  - University of Pittsburgh: Caribbean Basin Conference, 1981 March-1982 June (Box 117, Folder 1180)
  - University of Pittsburgh: Caribbean Basin Conference, 1982 December-1985 January (Box 117, Folder 1181)
  - University of Pittsburgh: Caribbean Basin Conference: Supplementary Material (I): "Cuba in the World", edited by Cole Balsier and Carmelo Mesa-Lago, 1979 (Box 117, Folder 1182)
  - University of Pittsburgh: Caribbean Basin Conference: Supplementary Material (II): "Confrontation in the Caribbean Basin", edited by Alan Adelman and Reid Reading, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 1183)
  - University of South Carolina: Soviets-Afghanistan, 1983 October-1985 April, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 1184)
  - University of Texas at El Paso: Julius Rivera: Front of File and Evaluation, 1976-1978, 1984-1985 (Box 118, Folder 1185)
  - University of Texas at El Paso: Julius Rivera, 1975 May-December (Box 118, Folder 1186)
  - University of Texas at El Paso: Julius Rivera, 1976 February-August (Box 118, Folder 1187)
  - University of Texas at El Paso: Julius Rivera, 1977 January-1979 October (Box 118, Folder 1188)
  - University of Texas at El Paso: Julius Rivera, 1980 July-August, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 1189)
  - University of Washington: Japan Conference, 1982 October-1983 October, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 1190)
  - University of Wisconsin: Energy Management in Mexico: Front of File and Evaluation, 1981-1982, 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 1191)
  - University of Wisconsin: Energy Management in Mexico, 1976 November, 1979 February-November (Box 118, Folder 1192)
  - University of Wisconsin: Energy Management in Mexico, 1980 November-1982 December (Box 118, Folder 1193)
  - University of Wisconsin: Energy Management in Mexico, 1983 February-1986 August (Box 118, Folder 1194)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: Chiawelo Community Project [CANCELLED], 1981 January-1984 August (Box 118, Folder 1195)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: Chiawelo Community Project: Supplementary Material [CANCELLED], 1979-1982 (Box 119, Folder 1196)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: Limehill Community Project: Front of File, 1982-1983, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 1197)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: Limehill Community Project, 1983 May (Box 119, Folder 1198)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: Limehill Community Project, 1983 June-1984 March (Box 119, Folder 1199)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: Limehill Community Project, 1984 August-1986 February (Box 119, Folder 1200)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: Limehill Community Project, 1986 March-1987 February (Box 119, Folder 1201)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: National Craft Association: Front of File, 1986, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 1202)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: National Craft Association, 1985-1986 July, no date (Box 119, Folder 1203)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: National Craft Association, 1986 August-October (Box 119, Folder 1204)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: National Craft Association, 1986 November-1988 August (Box 119, Folder 1205)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: National Craft Association, 1988 December-1990 August (Box 119, Folder 1206)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: National Craft Association, 1990 December-1991 October (Box 120, Folder 1207)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: Port Elizabeth Self Help Development Association: Front of File, 1985-1986, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 1208)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: Port Elizabeth Self Help Development Association, 1985-1986 September (Box 120, Folder 1209)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: Port Elizabeth Self Help Development Association, 1987 May-1988 December (Box 120, Folder 1210)
  - (489) – Wilgespruit Fellowship Centre: Port Elizabeth Self Help Development Association, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 1211)
  - Willrich Honorary Project (Not Completed), 1980 January-May, no date (Box 120, Folder 1212)
  - Willrich Honorary Project (Not Completed), 1980 June-July (Box 120, Folder 1213)
  - Willrich Honorary Project (Not Completed), 1980 July-October (Box 120, Folder 1214)
  - Willrich Honorary Project (Not Completed), 1980 November-1981 April, no date (Box 120, Folder 1215)
  - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy: Soviet-American Dialogue: Front of File, 1983, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 1216)
  - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy: Soviet-American Dialogue, 1983 July-December (Box 120, Folder 1217)
  - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy: Soviet-American Dialogue, 1984 September-December (Box 120, Folder 1218)
  - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy: Soviet-American Dialogue, 1984 December (Box 121, Folder 1219)
  - Women and Foundations/Corporate Philanthropy: Soviet-American Dialogue, 1985 July (Box 121, Folder 1220)
  - Yale University: Poland Conference, 1983 September-1984 September, 1986 (Box 121, Folder 1221)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II): Proposed Staff Accommodation for SCOPE Project, 1975 April; Proposed Staff Accommodation for SCOPE Project, Octagon Building, College of St. Mark and St. John, Kings Rd., Chelsea, SW10. Architectural Drawing, no date. Enclosed in Rita Jefferson (for T. F. Malone) to Elmore Jackson, April 1, 1975. Removed from Box 31, Folder 337.; Oversized material. (Box 143, Folder 1468)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II): International Council of Scientific Unions (ICSU) Organizational Chart, 1975 April; International Council of Scientific Unions (ICSU), Organizational Chart, September 1974. Enclosed in E. C. Rowan to Elmore Jackson, April 2, 1975. Removed from Box 31, Folder 337.; Oversized material. (Box 143, Folder 1469)
  - Council of Unions of South Africa: Working Women: Newspaper: IZWILETHU, 1985 October-1986 August; Newspaper: IZWILWETHU. Official Newsletter of the Council of Unions of South Africa. Volume 3, Nos. 7 and 8, August-October 1985. Removed from Box 48, Folder 525.; Oversized material. (Box 143, Folder 1470)
  - Grassroots Publications: Media Training: Supplementary Material (II): Posters, 1985, no date; Poster: "Grassroots Competition. Izwi Lolutshe Youth Express. International Youth Year 1985; Participation - Development - Peace." 1985. Poster: "Grassroots Concert. Youth Jive! Mapantsulas, Basil Goetzee, Amajinqi, Work Force, Sharptown Swingsters. Rocklands Civic, Fri. Aug. 9th. 8 pm. Donation R3,000." no date Poster: "We Want Peace and Friendship." no date Removed from Box 57, Folder 624.; Oversized material. (Box 143, Folder 1471)
  - Grassroots Publications: Newspaper "Learning Roots": Supplementary Material: "Learning Roots: The Student Paper", 1985-1986, 1988; Newspaper: "Learning Roots: The Student Paper". 11 issues. 1985, Nos. 2-6, April, June, August, September, October. 1986, Vol. 2, Nos. 1-2, February, April. 1988, Vol. 4, Nos. 1-4, February, March, April, June. Removed from Box 57, Folder 628; Oversized material. (Box 143, Folder 1472)
  - Grassroots Publications: Newspaper "Learning Roots": Supplementary Material: Newspaper: "South", 1988; Newspaper: "South". 2 issues. 1988 May 4-11. 1988 Mayh 10-19. Removed from Box 57, Folder 628.; Oversized material. (Box 143, Folder 1473)
  - Institute for East-West Security Studies: Middle East Conference: Supplementary Material (III): Broadside, 1985 June 14; Broadside: "The Dynamics of East-West Relations." Conference at Middlebury College, Middlebury, Vermont, October 11-14, 1984. Enclosed in John Edwin Mroz to John Stremlau, June 14, 1985. Removed from Box 59, Folder 650.; Oversized material. (Box 143, Folder 1474)
  - International Peace Academy: Newsletter, 1980-1981; Newsletter: "Coping with Conflict: A Review of the Work and Progress of the International Peace Academy, Inc.", Volume Three, 1979/80. Removed from Box 63, Folder 700.; Oversized material. (Box 143, Folder 1475)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology: Broadside: BOSTID, 1981-1982; Broadside: BOSTID: The Board of Science and Technology for International Development. Commission on International Relations, National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council, Washington, D.C., United States of America. No date. Removed from Box 75, Folder 830.; Oversized material. (Box 143, Folder 1476)
  - Conflict in International Relations - Fellowships, 155E
    - Vinod K. Aggarwal, 1983-1986, 1989-1990 (Box 121, Folder 1222)
    - G. Anandalingam: Front of File, 1970, 1982, 1984, 1986 (Box 121, Folder 1223)
    - G. Anandalingam, 1981-1982 (Box 121, Folder 1224)
    - G. Anandalingam, 1983-1985 (Box 121, Folder 1225)
    - G. Anandalingam: Supplementary Material (I), 1982-1984 (Box 121, Folder 1226)
    - G. Anandalingam: Supplementary Material (II), 1984, no date (Box 121, Folder 1227)
    - Cristiano Antonelli: Front of File, 1982, 1984, 1986 (Box 121, Folder 1228)
    - Cristiano Antonelli, 1981-1982 (Box 121, Folder 1229)
    - Cristiano Antonelli, 1983 (Box 122, Folder 1230)
    - Cristiano Antonelli, 1984-1985 (Box 122, Folder 1231)
    - Alexandre de Souza Costa Barros: Front of File, 1977-1978, 1985 (Box 122, Folder 1232)
    - Alexandre de Souza Costa Barros, 1976 (Box 122, Folder 1233)
    - Alexandre de Souza Costa Barros, 1977 (Box 122, Folder 1234)
    - Alexandre de Souza Costa Barros, 1978-1979, 1982-1984, no date (Box 122, Folder 1235)
    - Lawrence T. Caldwell: Front of File and Evaluation, 1975-1976, 1982-1983 (Box 122, Folder 1236)
    - Lawrence T. Caldwell, 1974 January-May (Box 122, Folder 1237)
    - Lawrence T. Caldwell, 1974 June-1975 September (Box 122, Folder 1238)
    - Lawrence T. Caldwell, 1975 November-1977 July, 1979 May-1980 November (Box 122, Folder 1239)
    - Lawrence T. Caldwell: Supplementary Material (I), 1975 (Box 122, Folder 1240)
    - Lawrence T.Caldwell: Supplementary Material (II), 1976, 1977 (Box 122, Folder 1241)
    - Lawrence T. Caldwell: Supplementary Material (III): "The Future of Soviet-American Relations", pp. 18-133, no date (Box 122, Folder 1242)
    - Lawrence T. Caldwell: Supplementary Material (IV): "The Future of Soviet-American Relations", pp. 135-230, 294-302, no date (Box 122, Folder 1243)
    - Luther J. Carter: Front of File, 1980, 1983-1984 (Box 123, Folder 1244)
    - Luther J. Carter, 1979 January-September (Box 123, Folder 1245)
    - Luther J. Carter, 1979 October-1984 February (Box 123, Folder 1246)
    - Luther J. Carter: Supplementary Material: "Nuclear Imperatives and Public Trust", 1987 (Box 123, Folder 1247)
    - Graciela Chichilnisky: Front of File, 1981, 1983, 1986 (Box 123, Folder 1248)
    - Graciela Chichilnisky, 1980 October-1982 August (Box 123, Folder 1249)
    - Graciela Chichilnisky, 1982 November (Box 123, Folder 1250)
    - Graciela Chichilnisky, 1982 November-1985 February (Box 123, Folder 1251)
    - Stephen D. Cohen: Front of File and Evaluation, 1975, 1980, 1983 (Box 123, Folder 1252)
    - Stephen D. Cohen, 1975 April-October (Box 123, Folder 1253)
    - Stephen D. Cohen, 1976 January-1977 November, 1979 May (Box 123, Folder 1254)
    - Stephen D. Cohen: Supplementary Material: "The Making of United States International Economic Policy", 1977 (Box 123, Folder 1255)
    - Peter F. Cowhey, 1983 January-1986 October, 1989 November, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 1256)
    - Richard S. Dale: Front of File, 1981, 1983, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 1257)
    - Richard S. Dale, 1980 October-November (Box 124, Folder 1258)
    - Richard S. Dale, 1981 February-November (Box 124, Folder 1259)
    - Richard S. Dale, 1982 January-1985 January (Box 124, Folder 1260)
    - Richard S. Dale: Supplementary Material (I): "Anti-Dumping Law in a Liberal Trade Order", 1980 (Box 124, Folder 1261)
    - Richard S. Dale: Supplementary Material (II): "Bank Supervision Around the World", 1982 (Box 124, Folder 1262)
    - Richard S. Dale: Supplementary Material (III): "The Regulation of International Banking", 1984 (Box 124, Folder 1263)
    - Karen Lea Dawisha: Front of File, 1982-1983, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 1264)
    - Karen Lea Dawisha, 1975, 1980, no date (Box 124, Folder 1265)
    - Karen Lea Dawisha, 1981 February-1983 March (Box 124, Folder 1266)
    - Karen Lea Dawisha, 1983 April-1985 January (Box 125, Folder 1267)
    - David A. Deese: Front of File and Evaluation, 1977, 1984, 1986 (Box 125, Folder 1268)
    - David A. Deese, 1977 April-October (Box 125, Folder 1269)
    - David A. Deese, 1977 November-1979 May (Box 125, Folder 1270)
    - David A. Deese, 1979 July-December, 1984 October (Box 125, Folder 1271)
    - David A. Deese: Supplementary Material: "Nuclear Proliferation: The Spent Fuel Problem", edited by Frederick C. Williams and David A. Deese, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 1272)
    - Susan E. Eckstein: Front of File and Evaluation, 1976, 1978, 1984, 1985 (Box 125, Folder 1273)
    - Susan E. Eckstein, 1975 September-November (Box 125, Folder 1274)
    - Susan E. Eckstein, 1975 December-1979 May (Box 125, Folder 1275)
    - Susan E. Eckstein, 1979 June-July (Box 125, Folder 1276)
    - Susan E. Eckstein, 1983 December (Box 125, Folder 1277)
    - Joshua M. Epstein: Front of File and Evaluation, 1983, 1985, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 126, Folder 1278)
    - Joshua M. Epstein, 1981 November-1983 April (Box 126, Folder 1279)
    - Joshua M. Epstein, 1983 May-1986 February (Box 126, Folder 1280)
    - Joshua M. Epstein: Supplementary Material (I): Publications - "International Security", "Orbis", 1981-1984 (Box 126, Folder 1281)
    - Joshua M. Epstein: Supplementary Material (II): "Strategy and Force Planning: The Case of the Persian Gulf", 1987 (Box 126, Folder 1282)
    - Connie M. Friesen: Front of File and Evaluation, 1983, 1986, 1988, 1990, no date (Box 126, Folder 1283)
    - Connie M. Friesen, 1983 January-July (Box 126, Folder 1284)
    - Connie M. Friesen, 1983 January (Box 126, Folder 1284A)
    - Connie M. Friesen, 1983 August-December (Box 126, Folder 1285)
    - Connie M. Friesen, 1984 March-1985 January (Box 126, Folder 1286)
    - Connie M. Friesen, 1985 March (Box 126, Folder 1287)
    - Connie M. Friesen, 1985 April-1986 November (Box 126, Folder 1288)
    - Alexander L. George: Front of File, 1979-1982, 1984 (Box 126, Folder 1289)
    - Alexander L. George, 1979 January-February (Box 126, Folder 1290)
    - Alexander L. George, 1979 April-1980 February (Box 126, Folder 1291)
    - Alexander L. George, 1980 May-1983 October (Box 126, Folder 1292)
    - Robert Gilpin, 1975 October-1981 November, 1982-1984 (Box 127, Folder 1293)
    - Robert Gilpin: Supplementary Material (I): "Change and War in World Politics", pp. i-iv, 1-61A, no date (Box 127, Folder 1294)
    - Robert Gilpin: Supplementary Material (II): "Change and War in World Politics", pp. 74-138A, no date (Box 127, Folder 1295)
    - Robert Gilpin: Supplementary Material (III): "Change and War in World Politics", pp. 139-218, no date (Box 127, Folder 1296)
    - Robert Gilpin: Supplementary Material (IV): "Change and War in World Politics", pp. 219-274, no date (Box 127, Folder 1297)
    - Louis Wolf Goodman: Front of File and Evaluation, 1978, 1982-1984 (Box 127, Folder 1298)
    - Louis Wolf Goodman, 1977 December-1981 August (Box 127, Folder 1299)
    - Gillian Gunn: Front of File, 1984, 1985, 1990 (Box 127, Folder 1300)
    - Gillian Gunn, 1983 January-1984 November (Box 127, Folder 1301)
    - Gillian Gunn, 1984 December (Box 127, Folder 1302)
    - Gillian Gunn, 1985 February-1986 November (Box 127, Folder 1303)
    - William W. Harris, 1981-1984, 1986, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 1304)
    - William W. Harris: Supplementary Material: "Taking Root: Israeli Settlement in the West Bank, the Golan and Gaza-Sinai, 1967-1980" (Box 127, Folder 1305)
    - Donald L. Horowitz: Front of File and Evaluation, 1976-1977, 1983-1984, 1989 (Box 128, Folder 1306)
    - Donald L. Horowitz, 1976 May-1979 May (Box 128, Folder 1307)
    - Donald L. Horowitz, 1980 October, 1983 October (Box 128, Folder 1308)
    - Germaine Hoston, 1983, 1985-1988, 1990, 1992 (Box 128, Folder 1309)
    - Germaine Hoston, 1983 (Box 128, Folder 1309A)
    - Roberto Y. Hukai: Front of File, 1978, 1984, 1985 (Box 128, Folder 1310)
    - Roberto Y. Hukai, 1977 April-December (Box 128, Folder 1311)
    - Roberto Y. Hukai, 1978 January-1979 September (Box 128, Folder 1312)
    - Peter A. Iseman, 1979 January-July, 1982 March-June, 1983 (Box 128, Folder 1313)
    - Enzhu Jiang, 1980 November-1983 February, 1985 (Box 128, Folder 1314)
    - Miles Kahler, 1983, 1985-1988, 1990, 1992 (Box 128, Folder 1315)
    - Miles Kahler, 1983 (Box 128, Folder 1315A)
    - Fuji Kamiya, 1976-1979, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 1316)
    - Mark N. Katz: Front of File and Evaluation, 1982, 1985-1987 (Box 129, Folder 1317)
    - Mark N. Katz, 1981-1986 (Box 129, Folder 1318)
    - Mark N. Katz: Supplementary Material (I): "The Soviet-Cuban Connection", 1984 (Box 129, Folder 1319)
    - Mark N. Katz: Supplementary Material (II): "Russia & Arabia", 1986 (Box 129, Folder 1320)
    - Mark N. Katz: Supplementary Material (III): "Russia and Arabia: Soviet Foreign Policy Toward the Arabian Peninsula", Introduction, pp. 1-21, no date (Box 129, Folder 1321)
    - Mark N. Katz: Supplementary Material (IV): "Russia and Arabia: Soviet Foreign Policy Toward the Arabian Peninsula", North Yemen, pp. 1-53, no date (Box 129, Folder 1322)
    - Mark N. Katz: Supplementary Material (V): "Russia and Arabia: Soviet Foreign Policy Toward the Arabian Peninsula", North Yemen, pp. 54-106, no date (Box 129, Folder 1323)
    - Mark N. Katz: Supplementary Material (VI): "Russia and Arabia: Soviet Foreign Policy Toward the Arabian Peninsula", South Yemen, pp. 1-45, no date (Box 129, Folder 1324)
    - Mark N. Katz: Supplementary Material (VII): "Russia and Arabia: Soviet Foreign Policy Toward the Arabian Peninsula", South Yemen, pp. 46-99, no date (Box 129, Folder 1325)
    - Mark N. Katz: Supplementary Material (VIII): "Russia and Arabia: Soviet Foreign Policy Toward the Arabian Peninsula", Oman, pp. 1-56, no date (Box 129, Folder 1326)
    - Mark N. Katz: Supplementary Material (IX): "Russia and Arabia: Soviet Foreign Policy Toward the Arabian Peninsula", Saudi Arabia, pp. 1-67, no date (Box 129, Folder 1327)
    - Mark N. Katz: Supplementary Material (X): "Russia and Arabia: Soviet Foreign Policy Toward the Arabian Peninsula", Kuwait, the U. A. E., Bahrain, and Qatar, pp. 1-65, no date (Box 129, Folder 1328)
    - Mark N. Katz: Supplementary Material (XI): "Russia and Arabia: Soviet Foreign Policy Toward the Arabian Peninsula", Conclusion, pp. 1-25, no date (Box 129, Folder 1329)
    - Peter J. Katzenstein: Front of File and Evaluation, 1977, 1979, 1981-1983 (Box 130, Folder 1330)
    - Peter J. Katzenstein, 1976-1980, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 1331)
    - Peter J. Katzenstein: Receipts, 1977-1979 (Box 130, Folder 1332)
    - Peter J. Katzenstein: Supplementary Material (I): "Dependence and Autonomy: Austria in an Interdependent World", 1979 (Box 130, Folder 1333)
    - Peter J. Katzenstein: Supplementary Material (II): "State Strength through Market Competition: Japan's Industrial Strategy", 1980 March (Box 130, Folder 1334)
    - Peter J. Katzenstein: Supplementary Material (III): "The Last Old Nation: Austrian National Consciousness since 1945", no date (Box 130, Folder 1335)
    - Peter J. Katzenstein: Supplementary Material (IV): "Capitalism In One Country? Switzerland In The International Economy", 1980 January (Box 130, Folder 1336)
    - Peter J. Katzenstein: Supplementary Material (V): "Corporatism and Change", 1984 (Box 130, Folder 1337)
    - Robert J. Lieber: Front of File and Evaluation, 1978, 1982-1983 (Box 130, Folder 1338)
    - Robert J. Lieber, 1977 December-1978 May (Box 130, Folder 1339)
    - Robert J. Lieber, 1979 July-1980 April (Box 131, Folder 1340)
    - Linda Y. C. Lim: Front of File, 1981, 1983, 1985, no date (Box 131, Folder 1341)
    - Linda Y. C. Lim, 1980 October-1981 September (Box 131, Folder 1342)
    - Linda Y. C. Lim, 1982 January-1984 January (Box 131, Folder 1343)
    - Linda Y. C. Lim: Supplementary Material (I), 1977, 1978 (Box 131, Folder 1344)
    - Linda Y. C. Lim: Supplementary Material (II), 1979, 1980 (Box 131, Folder 1345)
    - Charles H. Lipson: Front of File and Evaluation, 1979-1980, 1982-1984 (Box 131, Folder 1346)
    - Charles H. Lipson, 1978-1979, no date (Box 131, Folder 1347)
    - Charles H. Lipson, 1980 January-1981 November (Box 131, Folder 1348)
    - Charles H. Lipson, 1981 Autumn-1982 June, no date (Box 131, Folder 1349)
    - Antonio Marquina Barrio, 1981-1986 (Box 131, Folder 1350)
    - Antonio Marquina Barrio: Supplementary Material (I), 1983 (Box 132, Folder 1351)
    - Antonia Marquina Barrio: Supplementary Material (II): "España en la Politica de Seguridad Occidental 1939-1986" (Box 132, Folder 1352)
    - Onkar Marwah: Front of File and Evaluation, 1977-1979, 1984-1986 (Box 132, Folder 1353)
    - Onkar Marwah, 1976 November (Box 132, Folder 1354)
    - Onkar Marwah, 1976 December-1982 January (Box 132, Folder 1355)
    - Onkar Marwah: Supplementary Material (I), 1980 (Box 133, Folder 1356)
    - Onkar Marwah: Supplementary Material (II): "Nuclear Power in Developing Countries", by James Everett Katz and Onkar S. Marwah, 1982 (Box 133, Folder 1357)
    - Janice McCormick, 1983-1985, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 1358)
    - Janice McCormick, 1983 (Box 133, Folder 1358A)
    - Walter Murgatroyd: Front of File and Evaluation, 1978, 1984 (Box 133, Folder 1359)
    - Walter Murgatroyd, 1977 November-1979 November (Box 133, Folder 1360)
    - Walter Murgatroyd, 1982 January-1984 February (Box 133, Folder 1361)
    - John V. O'Loughlin, 1980-1984 (Box 133, Folder 1362)
    - John V. O'Loughlin: Supplementary Material, 1973, 1977, 1979-1980 (Box 133, Folder 1363)
    - Bruce Parrott, 1976-1978, 1980-1983 (Box 134, Folder 1364)
    - Bruce Parrott: Supplementary Material (I): "Technology and the Soviet Polity: The Problem of Industrial Innovation, 1928-1973", 1976 (Box 134, Folder 1365)